2021年  3月  2日
你能看見嗎?
Can you see it?
呃 有一點 但看起來不錯
Uh, yeah, a little, but it looks good.
- 好 能幫我拍「開始」嗎?  - 嗯
- All right, can you slate for me?  - Mm-hmm.
好的 只要你準備好了
All right, whenever you're ready.
嗯 好的
Mmm, okay.
我們在亞利桑那州斯科茨代爾市很棒的丹尼餐廳
Uh, we are here in the beautiful Denny's in Scottsdale, Arizona,
我正要見我的第一個生物學意義親屬 塞繆爾
and I am about to meet my first biological relative, Samuel.
- 塞繆爾  - 塞繆爾
- Samuel.  - Samuel.
你想告訴他們你在這裡經常整晚醉酒嗎?
You gonna tell them about all the drunken nights here at this booth?
- 你不要... 你閉嘴  - 絕對重磅
- You do not... You keep your mouth shut.  - Grand Slam.
我想是他
I think that's him.
- 你覺得是他嗎?  - 嗯
- You think that's him?  - Mm-hmm.
是啊 他用現金付的打車費 肯定是他
Yeah, he's trying to pay the Uber with cash. That's definitely him.
- 塞繆爾?  - 對 是我
- Samuel?  - Yeah, it's me.
瑪格特
Margot.
好
Cool.
- 哇  - 哇
- Wow.  - Wow.
- 噢 這太瘋狂了 抱歉  - 不 不 我...
- Oh, this is crazy. Sorry.  - No, no, I'm...
我也不知道說什麼
uh, at a loss for words myself.
- 你餓了嗎?  - 是啊
- Are you hungry?  - Yeah, yeah.
那是...
Is that...
- 對了 那是克里斯  - 嘿 你好嗎?
- Yeah, it's Chris.  - Hey. How you doing?
你說這是拍一部紀錄片嗎?
So, you said that this is gonna be a documentary?
對 很奇怪 我從沒想過我會對自己做點什麼
Yeah. It's weird. I never thought I would ever do anything about myself.
感覺有點太自我
Feels kind of self-indulgent,
但克里斯堅持做
but Chris pushed me to do it.
她的故事太好了
Her story's too good.
- 給你一些水  - 謝謝
- Some waters for you.  - Thank you.
謝謝
Thank you.
實際上 我從來沒有...
I've actually, uh, never, uh, been...
在鏡頭前站過
in front of a camera before.
有相機嗎?
Any camera?
- 有  - 什麼?
- Yeah.  - What?
是的 但我們通常不會 呃... 拍照
Yeah, we're typically not supposed to be, um... photographed,
因為 你知道 虛榮是一種罪
'cause, you know, uh, vanity is a sin.
啊 對 對
Ah. Right, right.
但也有例外 如果長老允許的話
But there are exceptions, if our elders condone it.
對了 你在電話里說你離開了社區
Yeah, you had said on the phone that you left the community.
- 對吧?  - 對
- Right?  - Yeah.
這是多久以前的事?
And how long ago has it been?
大概...
About...
我想是七個月前
seven months, I think.
這對你養父母來說不好受嗎?
Is this weird for your adopted parents?
是的 但我能連真正家人都不知道
It is, but could I have gone on living the rest of my life
而繼續生活下去嗎?
not finding out who my real family was?
當然 那也很好
Yeah, it'd be fine,
但我認為對於我們這些被父母遺棄的人來說
but I think for a lot of us people who have been given up by their parents,
總是缺少了一些東西
there's always something missing.
總之
Anyway,
知道我來自哪裡對我來說真的很重要
to find out where I come from would be really special for me.
那肯定
Absolutely.
希望我能幫上忙
Hopefully I can help.
23andMe: 一家DNA鑒定公司
你怎麼會在23andMe上認識個阿米緒人?
How do you even meet an Amish dude on 23andMe?
- 這不是違反規則嗎?  - 他是在「遊歷實證期」
- Isn't that against the rules?  - He's on his Rumspringa.
- 那是什麼?  - 基本上是一年
- What's that?  - It's basically like a year
在此期間他們可以與外界接觸
where they get to see the outside world for themselves.
所以他到處旅行 你知道 做些零工
So he was floating around, you know, taking odd jobs.
然後他遇到一個女人 幫她建了個圍欄...
Then he meets this woman and builds her a pen...
雞捨
Chicken coop.
謝謝 雞捨 正確
Thank you. Chicken coop. Correct.
- 她完全被他迷住了  - 她像是孤獨型女人
Basically, she becomes obsessed with him. More of a cat-lady type, yeah.
你想講故事嗎?
Do you wanna tell the story?
- 我的錯 我的錯  - 很抱歉 如果你願意的話
- My bad, my bad.  - I'm sorry. 'Cause you can if you want.
反正 基本上是她在向他誇耀
Anyway, so basically she's bragging to him
她有25%的切諾基人血統
about how she's 25% Cherokee or whatever
並告訴他有關在線DNA測試的信息
and tells him about the online DNA test you can do.
所以他測了並得到一個匹配... 就是我
So he gets one, gets a match... it's me.
阿米緒：是一個嚴格恪守《聖經》教義的宗教派別
她是阿米緒人
She's Amish.
- 我不是阿米緒人  - 你是阿米緒人
- I am not Amish.  - You are Amish.
不是那麼回事
Not how that works.
你從醫院拿到的這個?
You got this from the hospital?
我不敢相信有人會這樣拋棄他們的孩子
I can't believe anyone would just abandon their baby like that.
這對你來說肯定很緊張
This must have been so intense for you.
是的 我可能已經看過這視頻100多次了
Yeah, I've probably watched that video over a hundred times,
每次看我都會有個新的問題
and I get a new question every time I watch it.
比如 她為什麼這麼做?
Like, why did she do it?
她為什麼開那麼遠的車就為了拋棄我?
Why did she drive so far away just to abandon me?
她也許還活著? 知道嗎
Is she even still alive? You know.
最奇怪的就是她抱著我的方式
What I think is weird about it is the way that she's holding me.
四處張望 好像她很害怕
Like, looking around like she's scared.
也許她只是擔心自己被發現
Maybe she was just worried she was gonna get caught.
- 是罪惡感嗎?  - 是的 我也這麼想
- Guilt, yeah?  - Yeah, I mean, that's what I think.
也許吧
Maybe.
我不知道
I don't know.
2021年  3月  9日
請注意 行李提取區的所有乘客
Attention, all passengers in the baggage claim area.
達美航空歡迎您來到紐約布法羅市
Delta would like to welcome you to Buffalo, New York.
- 我的招牌動作  - 傻瓜
- My signature shot.  - Spaz.
這裡 我來拿
Here, I got it.
這孩子好有勁
Damn. Kid is strong.
你知道的 農場工人 習慣於搬運重物
You know, farm labor. You get used to moving heavy stuff.
- 謝謝  - 這是什麼東西?
- Thanks.  - What is this stuff?
魔法 寶貝
Magic, baby.
迷你相機 無人機 LED燈
Lipstick cam, drone, LEDs.
- 我們不是來這裡玩的  - 對 顯然不是 好吧
- We're not fucking around over here.  - Yeah, clearly not. Okay.
我們的音響師說他開一輛綠色麵包車
Uh, our sound guy said he'd be in a green van.
噢 在那裡
Oh. Right there.
嘿
Hey.
好
Yes.
- 嘿  - 嘿... 噢
- Hey.  - Hey... Oh.
抱歉 機場要戴口罩 我有
Airport. Sorry, mask. I got it. Sick.
- 嘿  - 是戴爾嗎?
- Hey.  - Are you Dale?
- 是的  - 嘿 我是瑪格特
- Yeah.  - Hey, I'm Margot.
這是克里斯 攝影師
This is Chris, our DP. Hey.
- 我是山姆  - 嘿 戴爾
- This is Sam.  - Hey. Dale, Sam.
- 非常感謝你開車來接我們  - 應該的
- Thank you so much for picking up the van.  - Of course.
我來幫你們裝東西
Let's get you guys loaded up.
實際上這是他第一次飛行
It was his first flight ever, actually.
- 第一次飛行?  - 對
- First flight ever?  - Yeah.
- 是的  - 不是吧
- Yeah.  - No shit!
相機很不錯
That's a great camera.
- 請隨意點  - 好的 謝謝
- Make yourselves comfortable.  - Yeah, thank you.
- 我們都測試過了 你們可以...  - 噢 是啊
- We all got tested. Are you okay if we...  - Oh, yeah, yeah.
我已經感染五次新冠了
I got COVID, like, five times.
都沒事 寶貝
All good, baby.
- 真的?  - 是啊
Really? Yeah.
我是說 我確診過一次 但在那之後我經常感染
I mean, it was diagnosed once, but I think I kept getting it after that.
不知道為啥 我的身體很奇怪 但我還活著
Yeah, I don't know. My body is weird, but I'm alive.
說真的 非常感謝你來接我們
Seriously, thank you so much for getting us there.
反正我也沒什麼事 所以很樂意效勞
Yeah, of course. I had nothing going on, so this is great for me.
這裡的雪更大了
There's so much more snow up here.
噢 是的 天氣每天都在變化
Oh, yeah. Weather changes every day.
頭天下雪 第二天就變成泥濘
One day you got snow, next it's slush.
這就是必須要有拉鍊的原因...
That's why you gotta do these zip off...
我所有褲子都有拉鍊 所以...
I do all my pants with zip offs, so it's...
你穿著長褲 「噢 太熱了?」
You got pants. Oh, it's too hot out?
馬上可以變短褲 寶貝
Now you got shorts, baby.
到了後我給你們演示 把褲腿脫下來 這很棒
I'll show you when we get in. I'll throw the legs on, dude. It rules.
如果你明白我的意思 我得說女士更適合
And I gotta say, easy access for the ladies, if you know what I mean.
- 好吧  - 嘿 看那個
- Okay.  - Hey, look at that.
什麼?
What?
你心裡在想什麼?
What's going through your head?
很緊張 但很興奮
I'm nervous, but excited.
♪ 還是我們在尋找答案? ♪
♪ Or are we looking for an answer? ♪
♪ 當問題的思路太難理解時 ♪
♪ When the question's Way too hard to understand ♪
好的 剛剛經過穀倉
Okay, so just past the barn here.
這是岔道
The turnoff here.
- 這裡有手機信號嗎?  - 呃 沒有
- You have any service here?  - Uh, nope.
對 我也沒有
Yeah, me either.
天啊
Christ.
慢點 慢點
Slow, slow, slow.
好吧 就停在這裡
Okay, and you can stop here.
- 好了  - 哇 好可愛
- Okay.  - Wow, it's so cute.
噢 呃...
Oh, um...
你們在這裡稍等一下
You guys, actually, just give me a second here.
我馬上回來
I'll be back in one second.
塞繆爾
Samuel!
伊萊 回屋裡去
Eli, go back in the house.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
看起來不太好
That doesn't look great.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 夥計們 呃...
All right, guys, uh...
壞消息
bad news.
你沒想過提前打電話跟他們說我們要來?
So you didn't think to call ahead and let them know we were coming?
他們是該死的阿米緒人 夥計 他們沒電話
They're fucking Amish, dude. They don't have a phone.
噢
Oh.
- 沒錯  - 是啊
- Right.  - Yeah.
兩張床
Two beds.
好吧 我們必須搞清楚這點
Okay, we're gonna have to figure that out.
該死
Goddamn.
你必須教我怎麼做 你有方法嗎?
You gotta teach me how you do this. Do you have a system?
有 列一個清單 說明用途 確保它們放在正確的位置
Yeah, just make a list, account for it, make sure you put it in the right spot.
藍色的必須放在那個角落里
That blue one actually goes right there in that corner.
- 好了  - 很好
- There you go.  - Awesome.
嗯 知道嗎  這很簡單
Yeah, you know, it's pretty easy.
天哪 真狗
Man! GoPro.
這很棒 我喜歡它們
These rule. Love these.
你可以弄髒它 隨便扔它們 可以把它們弄濕
You can get them filthy, you can toss them around, you can get them wet.
是啊 你可以那麼做...
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you can do...
對 你可以用真狗做很多事 你說得對
Yeah, you can do a lot with the GoPros. Yeah, you're right.
- 你沒看見  - 我是說
- You missed it.  - I mean,
也許這是一個過程 你知道嗎?
like, maybe this is gonna be a process. You know?
也許山姆明天可以回去再試試
Maybe Sam can go back tomorrow and try again.
他已經離開他們了
I mean, he left 'em.
- 他們可能根本不想他回來  - 噓
- They probably don't even want him back.  - Shh.
停 我只是說
Stop. I'm just saying.
- 小聲點  - 我們可能得收留他
- Keep your voice down.  - We might have to adopt him.
他在那裡 你能冷靜點嗎?
He's right there. Can you chill?
我們會有辦法
We'll figure it out.
那是什麼?
What was that?
- 嗯  - 噢
- Mm-mmm.  - Oh. Oh.
男士先來 好嗎?
Gentlemen first, okay?
- 你打開的嗎?  - 不是
- Did you leave that open?  - No.
你真是個膽小鬼
You're such a scaredy-cat.
真可愛
It's adorable.
噢 天哪
Oh, gosh.
伊萊 你在這裡幹什麼?
Eli, what are you doing here?
這裡 我拿到了
Here. I got it.
- 呃 我可以嗎?  - 不用 沒事 謝謝
- Uh, may I?  - Oh, no, it's okay. Thank you.
噢 嗨 小狗
Oh, hi, puppy.
抱歉
Sorry.
這邊
This way.
好的 我在這邊 你們要睡個好覺
All right, I'm this way. So you guys sleep tight.
我就在裡面
I'll be, uh, in there.
- 早上見  - 晚安
- See you in the morning.  - Good night.
- 你的房間在這邊  - 搞什麼?
- Your room is over here.  - What the fuck?
哇
Wow.
噢 真漂亮
Oh, it's beautiful.
爐子邊上還有木頭
There's more wood by the stove.
- 如果你需要什麼 告訴我  - 好的
- If you need anything, let me know.  - Okay.
- 晚安  - 太好了 非常感謝
- Good night.  - It's perfect. Thank you so much.
嘿 雅各布 呃...
Hey, Jacob, actually, um...
謝謝你 這太好了 晚安
Thank you. That means so much. Good night.
好吧 他怎麼說?
Okay. So, what'd he say?
他說 「非常感謝你把伊萊帶回家」
He said,"Thank you so much for bringing Eli home,"
他真的很感激 所以我們可以呆幾天
and he's really grateful, so we can stay for a couple of days.
- 我們可以拍?  - 他說 「好的」
- With our cameras?  - He said,"Okay."
太好了
Hey! Yes!
這很奇怪 就像 我很...
It's so weird, like, I was so...
我是說 這是我遇到的第一個和我有親緣關係的人
I mean, it was the first people I've ever seen who are related to me.
- 是的 那是你的家人  - 我想知道我們是否長得像
- Yeah, that's your family.  - I was wondering if we'd look alike.
戴爾 你不適合躺在床上
Dale, you don't fit on the bed.
噢 是啊
Oh, yeah.
我習慣了 我在家裡睡地板
I'm used to it. I sleep on a full at home.
你為什麼睡地板? 你才兩米一高
Why do you sleep on a full? You're, like, 6'7".
我和我媽媽住一個房間 她把床佔了
I share a room with my mom, and she takes the queen.
- 你和你媽媽睡嗎?  - 是的
- You sleep with your mom?  - Yeah, yeah.
她和我住一起 所以...
She lives with me, so...
我不是... 是的
I don't... Yeah.
- 什麼?  - 很甜蜜
- What?  - That's sweet.
克里斯?
Chris?
克里斯? 什麼?
Chris? What?
看
Look.
怎麼了?
What's up?
- 搞什麼鬼?  - 現在才凌晨2點
- What the hell?  - It's, like, 00 in the morning.
那些是人嗎?
Are those people?
我希望是
Yeah, I hope so.
我是說 還能是什麼?
I mean, what else could it be?
他們好像要進入森林
It's like they're going into the forest.
搞什麼?
What the fuck?
好奇怪
That was weird.
2021年  3月  10日
今天早上我拍了些很棒的外景
I got some cool B-roll this morning.
麥圈
Froot Loops.
你知道他們可以吃麥圈嗎?
Did you know that they could eat Froot Loops?
這是麥片 不是電腦
It's cereal, dude, not a computer.
你不用客氣
You don't have to do this.
我喜歡你的裙子 很漂亮 是你做的吗?
I love your dress. It's so pretty. Did you make that?
不 沃爾瑪買的
No. It's from Walmart.
你有抖音嗎?
Do you have TikTok?
- 呃 不 我手機上沒有  - 我有 我給你看我拍的視頻
- Uh, no, not on my phone.  - I do. I gotta show you this video I made.
瑪麗 別胡鬧了
Mary, stop ruching around.
抱歉 萊維納 抱歉
Sorry, Levina. Sorry, sorry.
- 早上好  - 早上好
- Good morning.  - Good morning.
抱歉 我是想讓你們體驗下本地風情
Sorry. Just trying to give you some local flair.
意思是「你好嗎?"
It means,"How are you?"
- 嗨  - 嗨 伊萊
- Hi!  - Hi, Eli.
怎麼了 夥計?
What's up, dude?
呃...
Um...
嘿 伊萊 伊萊
Hey, Eli. Eli.
你們今天有什麼計劃 或者...
So do you all have any plans for the day, or...
嗯 我們想看看你家其他地方
Um, we would love to see the rest of your home.
是啊 是的 當然
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
像雅各布這樣的長者會感到有點緊張
I know the elders like Jacob can feel kind of intense,
但只要你和我一起 你就沒事
but as long as you stick with me, you'll be fine.
未經社區內任何人的同意 不要去接近他們
Don't approach anybody in the community without asking their permission.
他們都很友好 但可能有點害羞
Everybody's really nice, but they can be a little shy.
呃... 噢 要避開那些樹林 有熊
Um... Oh, the woods, I would avoid those. We get bears.
我會跟你們一起 但它們在冬天會變得很暴力
And I'll be with you, but they get kind of violent during the winter.
實際上 我們昨晚看到一些人進了森林 很晚了
Actually, we saw some people going into the woods last night, super late.
是的 可能是個狩獵派對
Yeah, that was probably a hunting party.
有人的牛被襲擊了 所以...
Somebody's cow got attacked, so...
- 噢 好吧  - 好
- Oh. Okay.  - Yeah.
我覺得每個人看起來都很年輕
I feel like everyone seems relatively young.
這家人在這裡住多久了?
So how long has the family been here?
很久了 我想大概有200年
A long time. About 200 years, I think.
- 200年?  - 對
- 200 years?  - Yeah.
小心這裡的火
Watch the fire here.
這就是車間
So this is the workshop.
- 修理馬蹄鐵 設備 輪子  - 哇
- Fix horseshoes, equipment, wheels.  - Wow.
他們很小就工作了
Work 'em young.
是的 每個人都有目標
Yeah, everyone has a purpose.
他不習慣陌生人 來吧
He's not used to strangers. Come on.
我媽媽在這裡時住在哪裡?
Where did my mom live when she was here?
她住在你樓上的房間 但現在只是當作儲藏室
I think she was in the room above yours, but we just use it as storage now.
噢
Oh.
- 你想看看穀倉嗎?  - 好啊
- You wanna see the barn?  - Yeah.
噢 天哪 這麼多牛
Oh, my gosh, there's so many cows.
- 袋子里裝的什麼?  - 嗯 是鹽
What's all the bags? Uh, it's salt.
是給動物和冰準備的
You know, for the animals and ice.
- 那些是豬嗎? 停下  - 我們有些豬
- Are those pigs? Stop.  - Also got some pigs.
來吧
Come on.
- 這裡有豬  - 好的 過來
- There's pigs.  - Okay, come on over.
夥計們 進來
Guys, get in.
- 它們真像...  - 戴爾 進來
- They really like...  - Dale, get in.
不 你不用拍攝
No, you don't have to get the shot.
你只需要體驗一下豬 好嗎?
Just, you have to experience the pigs, okay?
你可以用你的麥克風... 對
You could put your boom mic... Yeah.
錄下和它的對話
Yg-get his dialogue.
- 停  - 嘿 有什麼最新消息?
- Stop.  - Hey, what's the scoop?
- 先生 有什麼最新消息?  - 我也要拍這些傢伙
- Sir, what's the scoop?  - I gotta get a shot of these guys too.
- 太可愛了  - 他們都有...
- It's too cute.- Do they all have...
我该怎么说? 比如 漂亮的屁股?
How do I say this? Like, nice butts like that?
- 你們想看看閣樓嗎?  - 是的
- You guys wanna see the loft?  - Yes.
- 噢 嘿  - 噢 我的天 山姆
- Oh, hey.  - Oh, my God, Sam.
- 它很酷 對吧?  - 它很大
- It's pretty cool, right?  - It's huge.
嗯 我們有很多動物要餵養 尤其是在冬天
Well, we got a lot of animals to feed, especially during the winter.
- 很漂亮  - 你也要做我的工作?
- It's beautiful.  - You're gonna do my job too?
- 你在我取景框中心  - 這就是我們要做的?
- You're in the center of my frame.  - That's what we're doing?
- 該死 夥計  - 好吧
- Shit, man.  - Okay.
抱歉 你沒事吧?
Sorry. You okay?
- 沒事  - 很抱歉 那裡有個活板門
- Yeah.  - I'm so sorry. There's a bale drop there.
- 你必須小心點  - 那就不太好了
- You gotta be careful.  - That wouldn't have been too good.
差點變肉串 知道嗎?
Shish kebab, you know?
- 我沒注意到  - 沒事的
- I wasn't paying any attention.  - It's okay.
這周圍有很多窟窿
There's lots of holes around here.
- 我們離開這裡  - 我笨手笨腳 謝謝你
- Let's get you away from that.  - I'm a klutz. Thank you.
- 你還好嗎?  - 是的 我很好
- You good?  - Yeah, I'm fine.
- 我們從這裡下去  - 有洗手間嗎?
- Let's get down from this height.  - Is there a restroom?
她剛才把我嚇尿了...
I kind of peed a little when she...
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
我是瑪格特
I'm Margot.
我想我們之前還不認識 但現在認識了
I don't think I've met you guys yet, but, yeah, we've met.
- 那是克拉拉  - 克拉拉 嗨
- That's Clara.  - Clara, hi.
- 還有格雷斯  - 一隻狗
- And Grace.  - A dog!
它真可愛
He's so cute.
你們多大了?
How old are you guys?
- 我16歲  - 16歲?
- I'm 16.  - Sixteen?
你們都是16歲嗎?
Are you... You're all 16?
是啊 你們太小 不可能知道我媽媽
Yeah, so you guys are way too young to have known my mom.
但你們的父母有沒有提到過她?
But your parents, do they ever talk about her?
我媽媽說莎拉和一個英國人在一起
My mom said Sarah hooked up with an Englishman.
- 克拉拉  - 大家都知道
- Clara.  - Everyone knows it.
一個英國人?
An Englishman?
就是指社區外面的人
Just means someone outside the community.
比如... 一個本地人?
Oh, so, like... like, a local?
有人知道他是誰嗎?
Um, does anybody know who he was?
所以是外面的人讓她懷孕了?
So she got pregnant with an outsider?
可以想象這肯定不是很好
So I imagine that didn't go over very well.
我們有很多事要做
We have a lot of work to do.
如果我們做不完就會有麻煩 對嗎 克拉拉?
We'll get in trouble if we don't get to it. Right, Clara?
- 對 抱歉  - 對不起
- Yes, I'm sorry.  - Excuse us.
阿門
Amen.
我們有句諺語
We have a saying.
「風暴可以吹散一千片樹葉 但樹木會一直生長」
"The storm may scatter a thousand leaves, but the tree grows anew."
我們謙卑地感恩我們的姐妹瑪格特回家了
We are humbled and grateful to have our sister, Margot, returned to us.
主的旨意顯明瞭
The Lord's will unfolds,
我們接受祂期望我們做出的承諾和犧牲
and we accept the obligations and the sacrifices that he expects of us.
呃
Eh.
呃 非常感謝你允許我們來你家
Uh, thank you so much for allowing us into your home.
我非常感激
I am so grateful.
說真的 呃...
Seriously. Um...
我一直希望能見到大家
I've always hoped that I could meet you all,
所以這對我來說是很特別的時刻
so this is a really special moment for me.
謝謝你們
So thank you.
酷 酷
Dude, dude.
我覺得這是個鼓掌的時刻
I thought it was a clap moment.
開始
Begin.
我想要一些 但是...
I'd have some, but...
噢 對 對 對 對
Oh, right. Right, right, right.
他們照料小雞
They tend to the chickens.
- 漢堡包  - 漢堡包
- Hamburger.  - Hamburger.
雅各布肯定很喜歡你
Jacob definitely has a thing for you.
- 什麼?  - 他一直盯著你看
- What?  - He's always staring at you.
- 別那麼討厭  - 這東西怎麼了?
- Don't be gross.  - What's wrong with this thing?
充不上電
Nothing's charging.
- 它太舊了 輕搖它  - 這是她說的
- It's old. Just wiggle it.  - That's what she said.
傻瓜
Stupid.
我真的覺得每個人都參與其中的樣子很快樂
I actually thought it was really sweet the way everyone was so present.
什麼 你想加入他們嗎?
What, you wanna join 'em?
不 我是說 你最後一次
No, but I mean, when is the last time
吃飯沒看手機是什麼時候?
that you went to dinner and didn't look at your phone?
今晚
Tonight.
準確
Exactly.
夥計 關上它 冷死了
Dude, close it. It's freezing.
我沒聽到發電機聲音
I don't hear the genny.
又開始下雪了
And it's snowing again.
我可以修 但我已經穿上睡衣了
I'd fix it, but I'm already in my cammies.
太黑了
It's dark dark.
「睡衣」
"Cammies."
又下雪了
It's coming down.
該死
Shit.
噢 該死
Oh, shit!
該死的稻草人
Bitch-ass scarecrow.
這裡連只鳥都沒有
Ain't even no crows out here.
媽的
Fuck.
拜託 寶貝 現在別這麼對我
Come on, baby, don't do this to me now.
噢 天哪
Oh, Jesus.
孩子 你嚇到我了
Kid, you scared me.
夢遊症
Sleepwalker.
他時不時就會夢遊
He does it from time to time.
幸運的是你在外面
Lucky you were out here.
是的 發電機壞了
Yeah. Our generator died.
回裡面去 會凍著你的
Come back inside. The cold will bite you.
奇怪
Weird.
2021年  3月  11日
我的頭疼死了
My head is killing me.
- 怎麼回事?  - 因為氣壓
- What's up with that?  - Barometric pressure.
就像高原反應 是你的身體對清潔的空氣有反應
It's like altitude sickness, only your body's reacting to the clean air.
戴爾 你是隨機信息的百科全書
Dale, you are an encyclopedia of random information.
謝謝
Thank you.
你們昨晚聽到有人在閣樓上走動的聲音嗎?
Did you hear that sound again last night, like someone walking in the attic?
- 沒有 我睡死了  - 我也是
- No, I was knocked out.  - Same.
戴爾 你完全瘋了
Dale, you're completely insane.
拜託 修飾讓男人改頭換面
Come on. The makeover maketh the man.
- 這是她說的 對吧?  - 對
- That's what she said, right?  - Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
是的 戴爾
Yes, Dale!
嘿嘿 噢?
Hee-hee! Oh?
我們做什麼?
What do we think?
你們知道那個舞嗎? 月球漫步
You guys know that dance? A little moonwalk.
是啊 跳支舞 來吧 各位
Yeah, do the dance. Come on, everybody!
大家跟我跳舞
Everybody, dance with me.
你好 你好
Hello, hello.
挺適合你
Suits you.
♪ 昨日飛逝 ♪
♪ Yesterday birds away ♪
♪ 冬天祈禱的時候到了 ♪
♪ Winter's come Time to pray ♪
- 我們去和他們談談  - 好
- Let's go talk to 'em.  - Yeah.
♪ 酸奶和沸騰的乳清 ♪
♪ Sour milk And boiling whey ♪
♪ 倒下 倒下 倒下 ♪
♪ Down, down, down, down ♪
看 這是慢動作 它在一秒鐘內播放很多幀
See, that's slow motion. It's getting a whole bunch of frames for one second.
一秒鐘 一千張圖片
A thousand pictures, one second.
因此 你會看到所有複雜的細節
So it gets, like, the little details, intricacies of you.
水在那裡飛濺 人眼看不見的細節
The water splashing up right there. Stuff the human eye can't see.
嗯
Mmm.
我喜歡你的洋娃娃
I like your doll.
- 她叫什麼名字?  - 莎拉
- What's her name?  - Sarah.
- 是個好名字  - 謝謝
- That's a pretty name.  - Thanks.
知道嗎 那是我媽媽的名字
You know, that was my mom's name.
她很久以前住在這裡
She used to live here a long time ago.
她一直在這裡
She's still here.
- 你說什麼?  - 她不喜歡你
- What did you say?  - She doesn't like you.
誰不喜歡我?
Who doesn't like me?
等等 你...
Wait, y...
她就這樣丟下她的洋娃娃?
She just left her doll like that?
那是什麼?
What is that?
現在是凌晨3點 又有人在上面
It's 00 in the morning, and somebody's up there again.
連續第三晚
Third night in a row.
噢 媽的
Oh, fuck.
門開著
Door's open.
噢 媽的
Oh, fuck.
恐怖
Creepy.
你那病態的邪教  --莎拉
搞什麼?
What the fuck?
什麼?
What?
不可能
No fucking way.
那是什麼?
What is that?
餵?
Hello?
你肯定在開玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
媽的
Fuck.
我怎麼離開這裡?
How do I get out of here?
好吧
Okay.
媽的
Fuck.
天哪
God.
這會很好玩的
This is gonna be interesting.
2021年  3月  12日
- 那是什麼?  - 我不知道
- What was it?  - I don't know.
它看起來像一張臉 對吧?
I mean, it looks like a face, right?
肯定是其它原因
It's gotta be something else.
我是說 鏡頭失真
I mean, a lens distortion.
- 鏡頭失真?  - 嗯
- A lens distortion?  - Mmm.
看 這是... 不
Fucking... See, this is... No.
這就是我不喜歡舊農場的原因 它們總是鬧鬼
This is why I don't like creepy old farms. They're always haunted.
戴爾 你小聲點
Dale, keep your voice down.
我說真的 看看這個地方 告訴我它沒有鬧鬼
I'm serious. Look at this place. Tell me it's not fucking haunted.
真的 我表哥
Really, My cousin
格雷格曾在一個冷凍間里看到一個鬼
Greg saw a ghost in the walk-in freezer at a Cracker Barrel.
他去冷凍間里幹什麼?
What was he going in the walk-in freezer for?
- 他在那裡上班  - 好吧
- He worked there.  - Okay.
你真的相信這種鬼話嗎?
Are you really buying this shit?
我感覺到我身上有什麼東西
I mean, I felt something up there with me.
好吧
Okay.
那我們現在是幽靈獵人了嗎?
So, we're ghost hunters now. Is that it?
我想我參加的是一部著名紀錄片
'Cause I thought I signed up for a prestige documentary,
而不是那種可笑的鬼作秀
not a fringy ghost-farm cable show.
- 這不好笑 克里斯  - 它不是
- It's not funny, Chris.  - It's not.
我是說 就像那封信 那張可怕的畫
I mean, like, the letter, the creepy drawing.
然後小女孩說 「她一直在這裡」
And then the little girl saying,"She's still here."
我是說 發生過一些事
I mean, something is going on,
我覺得這和我媽媽有關
and it feels like it has something to do with my mom.
是的 就在那邊 很好
Yeah, right over there. That'd be great.
你準備好了 抱歉 只是確保...如果你能看到它也沒關係 好嗎?
You're set. Sorry, just making sure that... Doesn't matter if you can see it, right?
戴爾 退後兩步
Dale, two steps back.
看起來不錯
Looks good.
我要開始嗎?
Do I just start?
- 是的 等你準備好了  - 嗯
- Yeah, when you're ready.  - Mmm.
莎拉曾是 呃...
Sarah was, um...
莎拉曾是我們的野花
Sarah was our wildflower.
一個建立在
A nonconformist
同質基礎社區中長大的自由思想者
growing up in a community whose bedrock is homogeneity.
還有 呃...
And, uh...
呃...
Uh...
但是 呃...
But the, uh...
我是說
I mean,
當她還是個小女孩時 我們看到的是
What we all saw as spunky and free-spirited
充滿活力和自由精神 呃...
when she was a little girl, um...
但演變成了很黑暗的東西
i-it evolved into something much darker.
她有過幾次自殺的企圖
There were several attempts to take her own life.
什麼?
What?
當那失敗後 她懷孕了
When that didn't work, she got pregnant.
是個城裡男孩 她不肯告訴我們是誰
It was... It was a boy from town. She wouldn't tell us who.
我...
I...
我懷疑她這麼做純粹是出於怨恨
I suspect she did it purely out of spite,
當作... 反抗我們生活和規則
as a way to... to rail against our ways
的一種方式
and our rules.
然後 這起作用了
And, uh, that worked.
她被回避了
She was shunned.
回避
Shunned.
什麼 比如被送走?
What, like, sent away?
不 不
No, no.
回避就是在從群體中分離出來
Shunning is being separated from the flock.
單獨吃飯 單獨工作 單獨睡覺
You eat alone, you work alone, you sleep alone.
那... 那很痛苦 相信我
And that's... And that is painful, trust me.
我想這可能是她最終離開的原因
I suppose it could be what drove her away in the end.
我在我媽媽房間里找到這封信
I found this letter in my mom's room.
你昨晚在閣樓上
You were in the attic last night.
她這句是什麼意思
What did she mean when she said,
「你們無法得到我或我的孩子」?
"You can't have me or my baby"?
我們不允許非婚生子
We don't allow children out of wedlock.
莎拉被要求把她的孩子交給社區里另一對夫婦
Sarah was required to give her baby to another wedded couple in the community.
- 她被迫放棄了我?  - 沒錯
- She was forced to give me away?  - That's right.
太可怕了
That's horrible.
比把新生兒像垃圾一樣丟在地上
More horrible than leaving a newborn on the ground,
丟在人行道上更可怕嗎?
on the sidewalk like a piece of trash?
我愛莎拉
I loved Sarah.
她是我唯一的女兒 但她只想著自己
She was my only daughter, but she cared for nobody but herself.
那是她的病
That was her sickness.
我明白了
I get it.
他們對她做的事真惡心
It's shitty what they did to her.
是啊
Yeah.
但我是說 她做了正確的事 對嗎?
But I mean, she did the right thing though, right?
否則我將被永遠困在這裡
'Cause otherwise I would have been stuck here forever.
確實
For sure.
我...
I ke...
我一直在想那個小女孩
I keep thinking about that little girl.
她前幾天說的話
What she said the other day.
自從我...
I have this...
來這裡就有種奇怪的感覺
weird feeling she's still here,
她還在這裡 在我的肚子里
in the pit of my stomach, ever since I got here.
我不能把手指放在上面
I can't put my finger on it.
好吧 別再往前走了
All right, not much further.
無人機看到它就像是在這裡
The drone made it seem like it was right over here.
我覺得我現在好想吃肉丸意大利面
I think I would do, like, a spaghetti with meatballs right now.
你有那麼餓嗎?
Are you that hungry?
你們會吃人嗎?
Would you guys eat human?
不 我永遠不會吃人
No, I would never eat a human.
說實話 我會比我想承認的更快吃掉一個人
I would eat a person faster than I'd like to admit, to be honest.
嗯 這要留意了
Well, that's noted.
看上面 看看那個
Look up though. Look at that.
呢呢呢
Nyeh-nyeh-nyeh!
我們應該走多遠?
How far away are we supposed to go?
哇
Whoa.
對吧? 這就是我一直跟你們說的
Right? That's what I've been telling you about.
是個教堂 哇
So it's a church. Whoopee.
是啊 但他們為什麼要在這裡建教堂呢?
Yeah, but why would they build a church all the way back here?
在一英里之外
It's like a mile away.
肯定是那天晚上他們去的地方
Gotta be where they were going the other night.
有熊 鬼扯
Bears, my ass.
這說明有很多人經過這裡
That means a lot of people walking through here.
- 小心  - 小心腳下
- Be careful.  - Watch your step.
好的
Yeah.
「到此為止」
"So weit nicht weiter."
有人懂德語嗎?
Anyone speak German?
有 那上面說
Yeah, it says, um,
「香甜 美味的小雞雞」
"Sweet, nice wiener."
天哪
Man.
- 你會開鎖嗎?  - 當然 我是黑人
- Can you pick a lock?  - Of course. I'm Black.
請讓讓
Move aside, please.
不會吧
No way.
是呀 格雷格表哥過去一直用這偷東西
Yeah, cousin Greg used to boost stuff all the time.
- 電視 汽車 隨便什麼  - 抱歉
- You know, TVs, cars, whatever.  - Sorry.
格雷格表哥很忙啊
Cousin Greg's busy.
格雷格表哥在監獄里
Cousin Greg is in prison.
瞧
Voilà.
不 不 停下
No, no, stop!
這是禮拜堂 你們禁止進入 不准拍照
This is a house of worship. It's off limits to you. No cameras!
抱歉 行
Sorry. Yeah.
- 我們不帶攝像機可以進去嗎?  - 不行 抱歉
- Can we go inside without the cameras?  - No, I'm sorry.
這是不允許的
It's not permitted.
家裡午飯準備好了 跟我來
Lunch is ready back at the house. Come with me.
是的 謝謝
Yes. Thanks.
我們會吃什麼? 炸肉排還是香腸?
What are we doing? Like a schnitzel thing, or a sausage?
這是冒犯嗎? 我不知道這是不是偏見
Is that offensive? I don't know if that's stereotyping.
不適合我 不適合我
Not for me, not for me.
非常感謝你
Thank you so much.
看來還要吃一點
There seems to be a little more.
戴爾 給其他人留點
Dale, save some for everyone else.
噢 對 抱歉
Oh, yeah, sorry.
拜託
Dude.
嘿 介意我給你拍幾分鐘嗎?
Hey, mind if I film you for a moment?
媽的
Fuck.
- 嘿 嘿  - 噢 天哪
- Hey. Hey.  - Oh, my gosh.
給我拿急救箱來
Fetch me the first-aid kit.
那是什麼?
What is that?
不會吧
No way.
噓噓噓
Shh-shh-shh.
- 怎麼了?  - 噓 聽
- What's wrong?  - Shh. Listen.
什麼?
What?
那是什麼?
What is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
那是什麼?
What is that?
把燈關掉
Turn the light off.
- 他們會看到的 關掉  - 好的
- They're gonna see it. Turn it off.  - Okay, right.
什麼?
What?
嘿 我們回去吧
Hey, let's just go back.
或者靠近點
Or get closer.
我啥都沒看見
I can't see shit.
上樓去
Go upstairs.
按住她
Hold her down.
他們在做什麼?
What are they doing?
什麼?
What?
什麼? 不
What? No.
噢 該死
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
它開始蔓延
It's starting to spread.
我知道
I know,
我們必須馬上動手
We have to do it now.
她在說什麼?
What is she talking about?
我們跟著他們
We should follow them.
媽的
Fuck.
他們在做什麼?
What are they doing?
有什麼事搞砸了
Something fucked up.
- 他們為啥把它放在教堂里?  - 肯定不是為祝福它
- Why would they put it in a church?  - Definitely not to bless it.
2021年  3月  13日
我們在半夜聽到瘋狂的尖叫 死亡的聲音
We hear this insane screaming, dying noise in the middle of the night,
然後我們到那裡 看見山羊祭品
and then we go and there's, like, a goat sacrifice.
動物會生病 對嗎?
Look, animals get sick, right?
有些有先天缺陷
Some have birth defects.
我們沒法養它們照顧它們 我們做該做的事
We can't feed them, take care of them. We do what we have to.
好吧 那他們為什麼把山羊帶進教堂?
Okay, then why did they bring the goats into your church?
我告訴過你不要去教堂
I told you not to go in the church.
- 我們沒有去教堂 我們看到他們...  - 嘿 這是怎麼了?
- We didn't go in the church, we saw them...  - Hey, what's going on here?
什麼意思?
What do you mean?
我以為這是一部關於你出身的紀錄片
Thought this was supposed to be a documentary about where you're from.
現在你晚上偷偷溜出去
And now you're sneaking out at night,
並拍攝各種與你的事無關的東西
and you're filming all kinds of stuff that's not really your business.
我在努力幫你 但別讓我後悔
I'm trying to help you. Don't make me regret it.
我不知道我媽媽怎麼了
I don't know what happened to my mom,
但我覺得答案就在那座教堂里
but I feel like the answers are in that church.
他們顯然把山姆留下來監視我們
Well, they obviously left Sam behind to babysit us.
我們必須想法分散他的注意力
So we'll have to find a way to distract him.
好吧 誰先來?
All right, who's first?
你來
You got it.
來吧 戴爾
Let's go, Dale.
好吧
Okay.
你要把兩條繮繩都握在左手 好的
So you're gonna take both of these reins in your left hand. Good.
右手握著那個鞍頭
Right hand's gonna go around that pommel.
左腳應該踩在馬鐙上
Your left foot's gonna go in the stirrup.
然後...
And then...
緊緊抓住
Hold that tight.
喔
Whoa!
- 你沒事  - 嘿 看看你
- You're okay.  - Hey! Look at you.
- 我說過它喜歡你  - 雙手都握住繮繩
- I told you he likes you.  - Both hands on the reins.
好 好 雙手 雙手
Good, good. Both hands, both hands.
好吧 你沒事 你沒事
Okay. You're okay, you're okay.
玩得開心
Have fun.
- 不 不 不  - 嘿
- No, no, no.  - Hey!
噢
Oh!
- 嘿 停下  - 你做錯了
- Hey, stop!  - You wrong for that.
- 把繮繩往後拉  - 加油 戴爾
- Just pull back on the reins!  - Go, Dale.
我拉緊了
I'm squeezing!
停下 叫他停下來
Stop! Tell him to stop!
好吧
All right.
瞧
Voilà.
長椅在哪裡?
Where are the pews?
我以為這應該是個教堂
I thought this was supposed to be a church.
克里斯
Chris.
地板上有幅畫
There's paintings on the ground.
噢 是啊
Oh, yeah.
有點像我在閣樓上看到的一幅畫
Kind of looks like a drawing that I saw in the attic.
「阿斯莫德斯」
"Asmodeus."
我們必須保持警惕
害怕魔鬼在我們中間蔓延
搞什麼 老兄?
What the fuck, man?
「年少者和弱者將首先受苦」?
"The young and the weak will suffer first"?
「讓我們做出犧牲」
"Lest sacrifices be made."
那是什麼?
What is that?
好吧...
Okay...
那是太陽馬戲團的道具嗎?
Is that some, like, Cirque du Soleil stuff?
穀倉里也有這些
Saw those in the barn.
那是個大鐘
That's a big bell.
喲 瑪格特
Yo, Margot.
- 瑪格特?  - 這裡
- Margot?  - Here.
噢
Oh.
看
Look.
- 那是什麼?  - 我想是血
- What is that?  - I think it's blood.
好的 等一下
Okay, hold on one second.
就一會兒
Just one second.
什麼?
What?
- 這東西能滑動  - 別弄壞了
- This thing slides.  - Don't break it.
- 幫我推過去  - 為什麼?
- Help me push it over.  - Why?
一 二...
One, two...
好了
That's it.
不是吧
No way.
媽的
Fuck.
天哪
Holy fuck.
- 哇  - 好吧 又怎樣?
- Whoa.  - Okay, so what?
他們只是...
They just...
把死山羊扔下去?
threw the dead goats down there?
但為什麼呢?
But why?
我不知道 某種形式的...
I don't know, some sort of...
宗教習俗?
religious custom?
媽的
Fuck.
嘿 嘿 小心點
Hey, hey, be careful.
哇 哥們 那...
Whoa, dude, that's...
真他媽深 喲
that's fucking far, yo.
怎麼?
What?
- 去它的  - 什麼?
- Fuck it.  - Fuck what?
去它的什麼?
Fuck what?
- 什麼?  - 嗯
- What?  - Mm-mmm!
這次不要 我們都不知道這東西是否安全
Hard no this time. We don't even know if this thing is safe.
它在這兒 他們使用它是有原因的
It's here. I mean, they're using it for a reason.
好吧 瑪格特 我不能看著你這麼做 別這樣
Okay, Margot, I can't just stand here and let you do this. Come on, now.
克里斯 我們只有一次機會 我不會錯過
Chris, we get one shot, one chance. I'm not messing it up.
這太重要了
It's too important.
把相機給我 操縱滑輪 我們能做到
Just give me the camera. Man the pulley. We got this.
我們能做到
The fuck we got this.
你確定要做嗎?
You sure about this?
是的
Yes.
這很好
It's good.
我看起來酷嗎?
Do I look cool?
不 你看起來瘋了
No, you look crazy.
別動
Don't move.
謝謝
Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 只是... 慢慢轉動
Okay, just... let it out real slow.
慢點
Slow.
好吧
Okay.
- 你沒事吧?  - 沒事
- Are you okay?  - Yeah.
我很好 繼續放
Yeah, I'm good. Keep going.
你還好嗎?
You good?
是的
Yep.
天哪 那是什麼?
Jesus, what is that?
什麼?
What?
有一股氣味
There's a smell.
媽的
Fuck.
很難聞
It's pretty bad.
你沒事吧?
You okay?
沒事
Yeah.
我很好
I-I'm good.
搞什麼? 什麼?
What the fuck? What?
這裡到處都是十字架
There's crosses everywhere.
什麼?
What?
到處都是十字架
There's crosses everywhere.
你想繼續嗎?
Do you wanna keep going?
是啊
Yeah.
是的 繼續
Yeah, keep going.
噢
Ohh.
好吧
Okay.
我能看到底部了
I can see the bottom!
克... 克里斯?
Chr... Chris?
克里斯?
Chris?
卡住了
It's stuck.
等等 等等 有東西卡住了
Hold on. Hold on. Something's stuck.
很接近了
So fucking close.
如果我俯身就能夠著它
I think I can reach it if I lean.
嘿... 下面有東西
H... Hey, there's something down here!
一個房間
A room!
好
Right.
好吧 那是什麼?
Okay. Who was that?
等等 回來
Wait, go back.
天哪
holy shit!
嘿 克里斯 我好了 拉我上去
Hey, Chris, I'm done. Pull me up.
嘿 拜託 我說真的 把我拉上去
Hey, please. I'm serious. Pull me up.
克里斯?
Chris?
嘿 把我拉上去
Hey, pull me up!
聽著 如果你聽到它 你就會明白
Look, if you just listen to it, then you'll understand.
你會傷到自己的 你嚇死我了
You could've hurt yourself. You scared the shit out of me.
這就是我要說的
That's all I'm saying.
所以必須知道 至少要承認
It's gotta be known, like, acknowledged at least.
- 我聽到了 但它像...  - 好吧
- I'll listen to it, but it's like...  - Okay.
來吧
Come on.
我正在聽
I'm listening to it.
戴爾 那是酒嗎?
Dale, is that booze?
威士忌 夥計 我剛從馬上摔下來
Whiskey, man. I just fell off a fucking horse.
克里斯
Chris.
- 克里斯  - 好吧
- Chris!  - Okay.
拉我上來
Pull me up!
克里斯 把我拉上來
Chris, pull me up!
- 把我拉上來  - 往後倒
- Pull me up!  - Go back.
聽到了嗎?
You hear that?
下面有東西
There's something down there.
動物嗎?
An animal?
該死 他們把山羊扔到地底下
Shit, they're throwing goats down a mine shaft
三十米深的...
to feed an animal...
礦井里去餵動物?
in a cave a hundred feet underground?
這些混蛋
Fuck those guys.
2021年  3月  14日
呃 雅各布?
Um, Jacob?
雅各布·貝勒  歡迎
什麼?
What?
雅各布·貝勒 致 塞繆爾·貝勒
山姆 你從瑪戈特那裡聽到有什麼消息嗎?
媽的
Fuck.
什麼?
What?
哇 哇
Whoa, whoa.
電池? 完全沒電了
Battery? Totally fucking dead.
- 他們一直在監視我  - 什麼?
- They've been watching me.  - What?
山姆離開社區不是為發現自我 而是來找我的
Sam didn't leave the community to find himself. He left to find me.
- 這整件事就像計劃好的  - 好吧 冷靜 冷靜點
- This whole thing's like a fucking setup.  - Okay, just slow down. Slow down.
一切都好嗎?
Is everything all right?
是啊 我很好 謝謝
Yeah, I'm good, thank you.
很好
Good.
很高興聽到
It's good to hear.
好吧 等等 我以為他們不可能有電腦
Okay, wait. I thought they couldn't have computers.
克里斯 這些郵件都發送一年多了
Chris, the emails went back for over a year.
早在山姆聯繫我前
Way before Sam contacted me.
他們知道我住哪裡 他們有我的地址
I mean, they knew where I live. They have my address.
他們有我的照片
They fucking have pictures of me.
- 他們有我的課程表  - 搞什麼?
- They had my class schedule.  - What the fuck?
他們在監視我 他們帶我們來這裡顯然有目的
They were watching me. They clearly brought us here for a reason.
- 他們為什麼這樣做?  - 我他媽不知道
- Why would they do that?  - I don't fucking know.
我他媽不知道 但這把我嚇著了
I don't fucking know, but it's freaking me out.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
- 我想走了  - 好的 好 但怎麼走?
- I wanna go.  - Okay. Okay, okay. But how?
我們沒有車 沒有電話
We have no car, we have no phone,
30英里內沒有人
and there's no one around for 30 miles.
媽的
Fuck.
這太糟糕了
This is so fucked.
嘿
Hey.
明天
Tomorrow.
好嗎? 都會好的
Okay? It's all good.
明早第一件事就是進城給麵包車買電池
First thing in the morning, we'll head into town and get a battery for the van.
好嗎?
Okay?
戴爾 醒醒
Dale, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
媽的
Fuck.
醒醒
Wake up.
什麼?
What?
克里斯 醒醒
Chris, wake up.
拜託 醒醒
Please, wake up!
那他媽是誰?
Who the fuck is that?
2021年  3月  15日
瑪格特?
Margot?
克里斯
Chris.
噢 天哪
Oh, Jesus Christ.
嘿 瑪格特 瑪格特?
Hey, Margot. Margot?
你沒事吧?
Are you okay?
她還要休息
She's resting again.
她怎麼了?
What was wrong with her?
我認為是過度疲勞加上異常強烈的月經週期
I'd say it's exhaustion coupled with an unusually severe menstrual cycle.
她流了很多血 但她會好起來的
She lost a fair amount of blood, but she's going to be fine.
我們不是該送她去醫院嗎?
Well, shouldn't we take her to a hospital?
不 她不需要醫院 她需要休息
No, she doesn't need a hospital. She needs rest.
好吧 無意冒犯 但你真的是醫生嗎?
Okay, no offense, but are you even a real doctor?
聽著 讓她休息
Listen, let her get some rest.
如果她病情惡化 我們會送她去醫院
If her condition worsens, we'll get her to a hospital.
異常強烈的月經週期?
Unusually strong menstrual cycle?
你相信嗎?
Do you believe that?
老兄 這太蠢了 沒人經過
Man, this is so stupid. Nobody's coming.
你有更好的主意嗎?
You got a better idea?
我在附近沒看到有阿米緒人的配件店
I don't see any Amish auto part stores around here.
看
Look.
噢 啊
Oh! Ah!
- 感謝上帝  - 噢 太好了
- Thank God.  - Oh, fuck, man. Yes.
噢 感謝上帝
Oh, thank God.
我覺得是輛郵車 嘿
I think it's a mail truck. Hey!
- 嘿 夥計  - 你好
- Hey, man.  - Hey there.
你能載我們進城嗎? 我們的電池壞了
Will you give us a ride into town? Our battery died.
- 可以 沒關係  - 行嗎?
- Yeah. That's all right.  - Hop in?
- 上來吧  - 謝謝
- Come on in.  - Thank you.
非常感謝
Thank you so much.
你的相機真不錯
That's a nice camera you got.
嗯 我們在貝勒農場拍一部紀錄片
Yeah, we're shooting a documentary up at the Beiler farm.
是嗎? 紀錄片講的是什麼?
Oh, yeah? What's y'alls documentary about?
阿米緒人
Amish people.
- 阿米緒人?  - 對
- Amish people?  - Yeah.
你們住在貝勒農場嗎?
You guys staying at the Beiler farm?
是啊 實際上我們已經在那裡拍攝一周了
Yeah. Actually, we've been there for about a week now filming.
好吧 你們知道貝勒一家不是阿米緒人
Yeah, all right. Well, you know the Beilers ain't Amish.
什麼? 他們當然是
Uh, what? Of course they are.
你覺得他們是?
Think they are?
嘿 我在這條路線上跑了40多年
Hey, I've been working this route for over 40 years
認識50平方英里範圍內的每個家庭
and I know every family within a 50-square-mile area,
他們大多數是阿米緒人
and most of them are Amish.
他們都會告訴你...
Now, they all will tell you...
貝勒家不是阿米緒人
the Beilers ain't Amish.
- 需要什麼嗎?  - 汽車電池?
- Can I help you?  - Car battery?
- 型號?  - 31C
- Size?  - 31C.
我去幫你查一下 馬上回來
Let me go check for you. Be right back.
媽的 夥計
Fuck, man.
也許我們不該離開瑪格特
Maybe we shouldn't have left Margot, man.
他們為啥要假裝阿米緒人?
Why would they pretend to be Amish?
不知道 也許藏在顯眼的地方更安全吧?
I don't know. Maybe hiding in plain sight, right?
就像... 我不知道
It's like... I don't know.
他們看起來像阿米緒人 融入人群 游離在社會之外
They look like them, they blend in, they're off the grid.
真是個天才的主意
It's kind of a genius idea.
他們為什麼想成為阿米緒人? 有什麼目的?
Why would they need to be Amish? What's the point in that?
- 再說下電池型號?  - 31C
- What size battery was it again?  - Thirty-one C.
我在這裡沒找到 我去後面幫你找一下
Yeah, I'm not seeing it here. I'm gonna go check in the back for you.
嘿 你介意我們用下你的電腦嗎?
Hey, you mind if we use your Internet for a second?
- 一點也不 請隨意  - 好
- Not at all. Have at it.  - Cool.
只是別查任何奇怪的東西
Just don't look up anything weird.
媽的 戴爾
Fuck, Dale.
你想讓我查什麼? 「假阿米緒人」?
What do you want me to look up? "Fake Amish people"?
不 搜索「阿斯莫德斯」
No, search"Asmodeus."
- 阿斯莫德斯?  - 對
Asmodeus? Yeah.
是我們在教堂發現的名字
That's the name we found at the church.
「慾望 痛苦和憤怒的惡魔王子
"The demonic prince of lust, suffering and wrath.
阿斯莫德斯 或阿斯莫德奧斯 是九層地獄的霸主
Asmodeus, or Asmodaios, is the overlord of the Nine Hells.
他是惡魔之王...」
He is the prince of demons..."
我他媽就知道 夥計 這些人是魔鬼崇拜者
I fucking knew it, man. These people are devil worshippers.
點擊頂部的那個
Click that right there at the top.
「挪威的貝斯基特村受到瘟疫的困擾
"The Norwegian village of Beskytter was beset by a pestilence.
莊稼和牲畜都死了 鄰居以殘酷的暴行
Crops and livestock perished, neighbor turned against neighbor
對待他們的鄰居」
in abhorrent acts of violence."
和你在教堂看到的一樣
The same stuff you saw in the church.
「這被認為是惡魔阿斯莫德斯造成的
"It was believed to be the work of the demon, Asmodeus.
在他們的絕望中 村民求助於白女巫
In their desperation, the village turned to the White Witch for help.
據說女巫把惡魔困在一個上帝選中女人的身體里
It is said the witch trapped the demon inside a chosen woman of God,
她的身體是神聖的容器 能誘捕這個強大的實體
her body a holy vessel to ensnare the powerful entity.
通過她的血統 從女兒到女兒
Through her bloodline, from daughter to daughter,
惡魔阿斯莫德烏斯被傳遞下去 以免它被釋放到世上」
the demon, Asmodeus, be passed, lest it be unleashed upon the world."
媽的 夥計
Fuck, man.
他們把它們困在這些女人的身體里?
They trapped them inside these women's bodies?
好了 來吧
Okay, come on.
女巫與惡魔? 這些不是真的
Like, witches, demons? Like, th-that's not real.
即使不是真的 他們仍然可以...
Even if it's not real, they could still...
如果他們相信 那就考慮一下
If they believe it, then think about it.
瑪格特的媽媽跑了 對吧?
Margot's mom runs off, right?
她把孩子藏起來讓她遠離這些邪教混蛋
And she hides her baby to keep her away from these 邪教 motherfuckers,
但他們還是找到了她
but they still find her somehow
並引誘她回來做這些愚蠢的事
and they lure her back to do whatever this shit is to her.
好了 各位
All right, you guys.
我找到了最後的31C
Got the last 31C right here.
夥計 你真的幫了大忙
Shit, dude. You're a lifesaver, man.
好吧
All right.
媽的
Fuck.
好吧 我去裝這個電池 我們在家裡見
All right. I'm gonna go deal with this battery. Meet me at the house.
- 你不用幫忙嗎?  - 不用 去拿瑪格特和我們的東西
- You sure you don't need help?  - No, man. Just get Margot and our shit.
- 我們離開這裡  - 是啊 去他媽這地方
- Let's get the fuck out of here.  - Yeah. Fuck this place.
餵?
Hello?
山姆? 瑪格特?
Sam? Margot?
媽的 瑪麗
Fuck. Mary.
嘿 嘿 瑪麗 等等 不
Hey, hey. Mary. Wait, wait, wait. No.
嘿
Hey!
瑪麗 你爸爸呢?
Mary, Where's your dad?
瑪麗 開門
Mary, open up.
媽的
Fuck.
瑪格特 該走了
Margot, it is time to go.
搞什麼? 我們的東西 我們的東西呢?
What the fuck? Our shit. Where the fuck is our shit?
怎麼了? 山姆?
What is going on? Sam?
到底怎麼回事 山姆?
What the fuck is going on, Sam?
瑪格特在哪裡?
Where's Margot?
山姆?
Sam?
瑪格特在哪裡 夥計?
Where the fuck is Margot, man?
女人是地球上最強大的生物
Women are the most powerful creatures on Earth.
什麼?
What?
生命給予者
Givers of life.
這就是為什麼我們的姐妹要背負這個重擔
That is why our sisters bear this burden.
她們是唯一強大到足以阻止它的人
They're the only ones strong enough to hold him back.
是時候了
It's time.
呆在裡面鎖好門
Stay behind locked doors.
鈴聲停下之前不要出來
Don't come out until the bell stops ringing.
什麼? 等等 山姆
What? wait, Sam.
老兄 你要去哪裡? 山姆
Dude, where are you going? Sam!
瑪格特?
Margot?
好吧 冷靜點 夥計
Okay. Easy, man.
- 不要試圖阻止這事  - 把槍放下
- Don't try to stop this.  - Just put the gun down.
她的身體是唯一能容納惡魔的東西
Her body is the only thing that can hold the demon.
如果你放了它 它會佔據任何人的身體
If you set him free, he'll be able to possess anyone,
從一個身體轉另一個身體
jumping from body to body.
- 你要對她做什麼?  - 它會殺了我們
- What are you doing to her?  - He'll kill us all.
它會殺了我們所有人
He'll kill every last one of us.
把槍放下 夥計
Just put the gun down, man.
- 求你了 夥計  - 你不想這麼做
- Please, man.  - You don't want to do this.
媽的 噢 媽的
Fuck. Oh, fuck.
堅持住 瑪格特 我來了
Hold on, Margot. I'm coming.
噢... 天哪
Oh... Oh, God.
瑪格特? 媽的
Margot? Fuck.
瑪格特?
Margot?
媽的 好了 好了 媽的
Fuck. Okay, okay. Fuck.
好吧
Okay.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
瑪格特?
Margot?
瑪格特
Margot!
Margot.
搞什麼?
The fuck?
你在做什麼? 該死 你在對她做什麼?
What are you doing? Shit. What are you doing to her?
瑪格特 快他媽起來
Margot, get the fuck up!
媽的 瑪格特 停下
Fuck. Margot! Just stop it, all right.
我說停下
I said stop it.
瑪格特? 瑪格特 瑪格特
Margot? Margot. Margot.
- 媽的  - 鹽 鹽
- Fuck.  - The salt. The salt.
拜託 醒醒 瑪格特 快點 該走了
Please. Wake up, Margot. Come on. It's time to go.
- 瑪格特 起來  - 鹽 鹽
- Margot, get up.  - The salt. The salt.
瑪格特 快 起來 請醒醒
Margot, come on. Get up! Please wake up.
快點 好了 好了
Yeah. Come on. Yeah. Yeah.
不 不
No! No!
- 退後  - 不
- Back up!  - No!
退後 不然我他媽...
Back up or I'll fuckin'...
你不知道你在做什麼
You don't know what you're doing!
那是什麼鬼?
The fuck is that?
該死 瑪格特 快跑
Goddamn. Margot, run!
快跑 瑪格特 跑
Run, Margot! Run!
跑 快跑
Run! Fucking run!
快跑 瑪格特
Run, Margot!
跑 媽的
Run! Fuck!
那他媽是什麼?
What the fuck was that?
- 噢 媽的  - 不 不 不
- Oh, shit.  - No, no, no.
- 媽的 我們怎麼離開這裡?  - 肯定有出路
- Fuck! How are we gonna get out of here?  - There's gotta be a way out.
肯定有該死的出路
There's gotta be a fucking way out.
- 快 克里斯 快想辦法  - 有人嗎?
- Come on, Chris. Fucking think.  - Hello?
見鬼 戴爾?
Holy shit. Dale?
- 戴爾  - 是我們 你把我們拉上來 夥計
- Dale!  - It's us! We need you to pull us back up, man!
- 怎麼了 老兄?  - 我們被卡住了 用滑輪拉上來
- What's going on, man?  - We're stuck! Just pull up the pulley!
- 我們需要你拉滑輪  - 好的
- We need you to pull the pulley!  - Okay!
媽的 來吧
Fuck. Come on.
媽的 那是什麼鬼東西 夥計?
Holy fuck. What the fuck was that thing, man?
天哪 好了
Jesus. Okay.
抓住這個 快
Hold this. Come on.
好了 往上拉 戴爾
All right. Pull up now, Dale!
快 快 快 快
Now, now, now, now!
好
Okay.
你快到了 你快到了 你快到了
You're almost there. You're almost there. You're almost there.
快點 戴爾
Faster, Dale!
媽的
Fuck me.
好吧
Okay.
快點 夥計 快 夥計
Come on, man. Come on, man.
快點 媽的
Come on. Fuck.
好 好的
All right. Okay.
噢 該死
Oh, shit.
快點吧 夥計 快拉繩子 夥計 快
Come on, man! Pull the fucking rope now, man! Now!
感謝上帝
Thank God.
好吧 戴爾 拉我上去 拉我上去
All right, Dale. Pull me up. Pull me up, man.
快點 夥計 快 快 快
Faster, man. now, now, now!
噢 媽的 快拉 戴爾 把我拉上去
Oh, fuck! Pull me up, Dale! Pull me up!
把我拉上去
Pull me up!
快點 戴爾
Come on, Dale!
乾得好 是啊
Good job. Yeah.
我們快離開這裡 電池裝好了嗎?
We gotta get the fuck out of here. Did you fix the battery?
- 是的 好了  - 該死 我們走
- Yeah, it's ready.  - Shit. Let's go.
- 瑪格特  - 快 瑪格特
- Margot.  - Now, Margot.
搞什麼? 戴爾 走吧
What the fuck? Dale, just go.
不 不 不 媽的
No, no, no, no. Fuck.
不
No.
媽的
Fuck.
快跑 媽的 跑
Run! Fuck! Run!
它來了 快點 快
It's coming. Come on! Come on!
那是什麼東西 夥計?
What is that thing, man?
- 哪邊?  - 快 夥計 我什麼都看不見
- Which way?  - Come on, man. I can't see shit.
- 克里斯  - 戴爾 哪邊?
- Chris!  - Dale, which way?
瑪格特 你在哪裡?
Margot, where are you?
瑪格特
Margot!
那他媽是什麼?
What the fuck was that?
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
Oh, God!
快 我們開始行動 快點
Come on. Let's start moving. Come on.
這邊 這邊
This way. This way.
瑪格特?
Margot?
瑪格特? 你去哪了?
Margot? Where'd you go?
瑪格特?
Margot?
該死 瑪格特 你沒事吧?
Oh, shit. Margot, you okay?
瑪格特?
Margot?
瑪格特 瑪格特 噢 天哪
Margot, Margot, Margot. Oh, my God.
好吧 我會帶我們離開這裡
Okay. I'm gonna get us out of here.
該死 瑪格特 快跑 跑
Oh, shit. Margot, run. Run!
跑
Go!
該死
Shit.
我們走錯邊了
We're on the wrong side.
我們要翻過去到麵包車那裡
We need to get up and over to get to the van.
麵包車就在那裡
The van's right there.
- 好嗎?  - 好的
- Okay?  - Okay.
它在那裡
It's right there.
停下 放開他 莎拉
Stop! Get off of him! Sarah!
看著我
Look at me.
看著我的臉
Look at my face.
你能看見嗎?
Can you see?
你還記得我嗎?
Do you remember me?
是我
It's me.
你的女兒
Your daughter.
我現在來了...
I'm here now...
媽媽
Mom.
我在這裡
I'm here now.
該死 你沒事吧?
Fuck. Are you okay?
沒事
Yeah.
我們得走了
We gotta go.
我們走
Let's go.
好了 鎖上
Okay. Lock it.
好吧
Okay.
鑰匙 鑰匙
Keys. Keys.
你他媽把鑰匙放哪裡了?
Where the fuck you put the keys?
戴爾
Dale.
媽的
Fuck!
好吧
Okay.
我們必須找到它
We should go get it.
噢 天哪 不
Oh, my God. No.
好吧 拿著 讓我來
All right. Here. Here. I'll do it.
拿著小相機 把燈光照過來
Here's the little camera. Just shine that light over here.
好吧 鑰匙 鑰匙
Okay. Keys, keys, keys.
瑪格特 我們走 瑪格特 快 來吧 快
Margot, let's go. Margot, now. Come on. Now.
瑪格特 快 走吧
Margot, now. Let's go.
走吧
Let's go.
我們快到了 我們快到了
We're almost there. We're almost there.
好
Okay.
媽的 它在這裡
Fuck, It's here.
快點 快點
Come on. Come on.
媽的
Fuck me.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
快 快點 媽的
Come on. Come on. Fuck.
快 寶貝
Come on, baby.
天啊
Holy shit!
噢 該死
Oh, shit!
媽的
Fuck!
Fuck.
所有單位 請回應 在戈倫4277有疑似謀殺案
All available units, please respond. We have a possible 187 at 4277 Golen.
調度中心 我是921 我位於戈倫4277
Dispatch, this is 921. I'm at 4277 Golen.
貝勒農場
The Beiler farm.
警察
Sheriff's department!
媽的
Fuck.
調度中心 我發現多名死者 需要立即支援
Dispatch, I have multiple fatalities. Need assistance immediately.
天哪
Jesus Christ.
警察
Sheriff's department.
天啊
Holy shit.
搞什麼? 把手舉起來
What the fuck? Get your hands up.
讓我看見你的手 快
Let me see your hands! Now!
舉起手
Hands up!
搞什麼?
What the fuck?
調度中心 這是12單位 增援到達現場
Dispatch, this is unit 12. Backup arriving on scene.
天啊
Holy shit.
喔 喔 喔 放鬆點 夥計
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy, buddy.
放鬆 夥計
Easy, buddy.
東區12街773號
773 East 12th Street.
有人從建築物頂上扔磚頭
Someone is throwing bricks from the roof of the building.
你能達到拐角處嗎?
Can you try to reach the corner?
你確認可疑車輛嗎? 收到了嗎?
Do you affirm a 10-61? Can you copy?
確認 地址是什麼?
10-4. What's the address?
♪ 你好 親愛的 ♪
♪ Hello, darlin' ♪
♪ 很高興見到你 ♪
♪ Nice to see you ♪
♪ 好久不見了 ♪
♪ It's been a long time ♪
♪ 你還是那麼帥 ♪
♪ You're just as handsome ♪
♪ 就像你過去一樣 ♪
♪ As you used to be ♪
~ 導演  威廉·尤班克 ~
♪ 你的新歡怎麼樣? ♪
♪ How's your new love? ♪
~ 編劇  克里斯托弗·蘭登 ~
♪ 你快樂嗎? ♪
♪ Are you happy? ♪
♪ 希望你過得很好 ♪
♪ Hope you're doing fine ♪
~ 根據影片《鬼影實錄》改編 ~
奧倫·佩里
♪ 只是想知道 ♪
♪ Just to know it ♪
~ 製片 傑森·布魯姆 奧倫·佩里 ~
♪ 對我來說很重要 ♪
♪ Means so much to me ♪
♪ 那是什麼 親愛的? ♪
♪ What's that, darlin'? ♪
♪ 我過得怎樣? ♪
♪ How am I doin'? ♪
♪ 我過得很好 ♪
♪ I'm doin' all right ♪
♪ 除了我無法入眠 ♪
♪ Except I can't sleep ♪
♪ 我整夜哭泣直到黎明 ♪
♪ And I cry all night Till dawn ♪
♪ 我想說的 ♪
♪ What I'm trying to say ♪
主演
艾米麗·貝德
♪ 是我愛你嗎 ♪
♪ Is I love you ♪
主演
羅蘭·巴克三世
♪ 想你 ♪
♪ And miss you ♪
♪ 我很抱歉 ♪
♪ And I'm so sorry ♪
主演
丹·利珀特
♪ 我錯怪了你 ♪
♪ That I did you wrong ♪
主演
亨利·艾爾斯-布朗
♪ 抬頭看 親愛的 ♪
♪ Look up, darlin' ♪
~ 派拉蒙 原創 ~
電影
♪ 讓我吻你 ♪
♪ Let me kiss you ♪
♪ 看在過去的份上 ♪
♪ Just for old times' sake ♪
♪ 讓我抱著你 ♪
♪ Let me hold you ♪
♪ 在我臂彎中 ♪
♪ In my arms ♪
鬼影實錄6
♪ 再一次 ♪
♪ One more time ♪
近親
♪ 謝謝你 親愛的 ♪
♪ Thank you, darlin' ♪
♪ 願上帝保佑你 ♪
♪ May God bless you ♪
♪ 願你邁出的每一步 ♪
♪ And may each step You take ♪
♪ 都讓你更接近 ♪
♪ Bring you closer ♪
♪ 在尋找想要的東西 ♪
♪ To the things You seek to find ♪
♪ 再見 親愛的 ♪
♪ Goodbye, darlin' ♪
♪ 我得走了 ♪
♪ Gotta go now ♪
♪ 必須想辦法 ♪
♪ Gotta try to find a way ♪
♪ 忘掉這些記憶 ♪
♪ To lose these memories ♪
♪ 愛情 ♪
♪ Of a love ♪
♪ 如此溫暖和真實 ♪
♪ So warm and true ♪
♪ 如果你有機會 ♪
♪ And if you should ever ♪
♪ 在你心中找到它 ♪
♪ Find it in your heart ♪
♪ 原諒我 ♪
♪ To forgive me ♪
♪ 回來吧 親愛的 ♪
♪ Come back, darlin' ♪
♪ 我會等著你 ♪
♪ I'll be waiting for you ♪